



granen.n@gmail.com

Kojvikshöjden 3, Dalarö

Github

Linkedin

About me

I have a strong passion for programming & games.

Skills

Source Tree

Programming Languages Game Engines

C#

Unity

UF4

C++Java

NIKLAS GRANSKOG

Programmer

Futuregames was an education that specialized in teaching students about the gaming industry. As for the programmer course, the focus was on C# & Unity with some courses in C++ & Unreal Engine 4.

I would describe myself as a person that wants to not only improve my skills, but use those skills to the best of my ability.

Work Experience

Gamucatex 2023-01-09 - Ongoing

Internship, Programmer C#, Unity

- Custom Console (Replacement for Unity's Console)
- In game command console

2022-06-20 - 2023-02-06 Landell Games AB Internship, Programmer C#, Unity

- Photon Networking
- Gameplay
- · Damage System

Education

2020 Rekt Games

Internship, Gameplay Programmer C#, Unity

- Refactor similar gameplay elements with inheritance & polymorphism.
- Random AI movement for objects in the game scene.
- · Simple UI transition between scenes.

Futuregames University 2018 - 2021 Gameplay programmer C#/C++

 Programmer for game projects in Unity and Unreal Engine 4.

Languages

Swedish, native

English

Github Desktop Plastic SCM

Perforce